<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jason Hand</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jason Hand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Long Strange Trip It&#39;s Been</title>
      <link>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</guid>
      <description>Just over four years ago, I impulsively responded to a Facebook post about a devops evangelism role at a new tech startup.
I had never been an evangelist and I knew nothing of the term “devops”. #yolo ¯_(ツ)_/¯
This spontaneous act illuminated a path of personal and professional growth.
A path that created new opportunities for me almost daily.
A path that changed me for the better.
A path that wasn’t there… until it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>/gallery/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/books/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Range SRE Meetup</title>
      <link>/gallery/frontrangesre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/frontrangesre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Pulse</title>
      <link>/gallery/communitypulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:16:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/communitypulse/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevopsDays Rockies</title>
      <link>/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo on Azure</title>
      <link>/blog/huto_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:37:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/huto_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>As I get settled in to my new role as a Cloud Ops Advocate for Microsft Azure, I&amp;rsquo;ve been kicking around ideas for both learning the Azure platform as well as showing off a few things you can do with the service.
Every so often I decide that my website (jasonhand.com) needs an overhaul. But then inevitably I run out of time or energy to not only design and launch a completely new site but to keep up with providing helpful content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Deployment Option</title>
      <link>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post is a continuation of &amp;ldquo;Deploy a Static HTML Site To Azure as a Web App&amp;rdquo;. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already deployed your new static HTML site following the steps outlined in that post, I suggest starting there first.
Now that our static HTML site is live, I want to take it one step further.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how often I&amp;rsquo;ll be making changes to the content of my site, but I know that I want to remove as many barriers to releasing new information as I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy a Static HTML Site To Azure as a Web App</title>
      <link>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 15:26:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial will walk you through getting a static web site up and running as a Web App on Microsoft Azure.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read my post &amp;ldquo;Hugo on Azure&amp;rdquo;, I suggest starting there. This post is a continuation of that conversation. We are taking a static HTML site built using Hugo and deploying it to a web server (web app actually) on Azure.
The site itself is stored in a GitHub repository:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Jason Hand Senior Cloud Ops Advocate @ Microsoft Jason Hand writes, presents, and coaches on the principles and nuance of DevOps, Site Reliability Engineering, and modern incident management practices. Named &amp;ldquo;DevOps Evangelist of the Year&amp;rdquo; by DevOps.com in 2016, Jason recently authored a new book on the topic of Site Reliability Engineering. In addition to SRE, Jason has authored books with O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media on the subject of post-incident reviews and Chatops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>