<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jason Hand</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jason Hand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:48 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>/gallery/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/books/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Long Strange Trip It&#39;s Been</title>
      <link>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</guid>
      <description>Just over four years ago, I impulsively responded to a Facebook post about a devops evangelism role at a new tech startup.
I had never been an evangelist and I knew nothing of the term “devops”. #yolo ¯_(ツ)_/¯
This spontaneous act illuminated a path of personal and professional growth.
A path that created new opportunities for me almost daily.
A path that changed me for the better.
A path that wasn’t there… until it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Range SRE Meetup</title>
      <link>/gallery/frontrangesre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/frontrangesre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Pulse</title>
      <link>/gallery/communitypulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:16:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/communitypulse/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevopsDays Rockies</title>
      <link>/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Auto Deployments</title>
      <link>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:00:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post is a continuation of &amp;ldquo;Six Easy Steps to Deploying Static HTML on Azure&amp;rdquo;. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already deployed your new static HTML site following the steps outlined in that post, I suggest starting there first.
Now that our static HTML site is live, I want to take it one step further.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how often I&amp;rsquo;ll be making changes to the content of my site, but I know that I want to remove as many barriers to releasing new information as I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Easy Steps to Deploying Static HTML on Azure</title>
      <link>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:26:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read my post &amp;ldquo;Hugo on Azure&amp;rdquo;, I suggest starting there.
This post will outline the following simple steps to deploy a static HTML website to an App Service on Azure.
 Login to Azure Launch CloudShell Mount (or Create) Persistent Storage Install Azure Web App Extension for CloudShell Clone Repository Deploy (HTML) Code  We are taking a static HTML site built using Hugo and deploying it to a web server (app service actually) on Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo on Azure</title>
      <link>/blog/hugo_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:37:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugo_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>This walk-through will cover the following:  Create an App Service (to host our website) Clone a GitHub repository (static HTML) to the App Service Configure Automatic Deployments from repository to the App Service Scale the App Service Up Configure a custom domain name to the App Service  While I slide in to my new role as a Cloud Ops Advocate for Microsft Azure, I&amp;rsquo;ve been kicking around ideas for both learning the platform as well as showing off a few things you can do with the service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Jason Hand Senior Cloud Ops Advocate @ Microsoft Jason Hand writes, presents, and coaches on the principles and nuance of DevOps, Site Reliability Engineering, and modern incident management practices. Named &amp;ldquo;DevOps Evangelist of the Year&amp;rdquo; by DevOps.com in 2016, Jason recently authored a new book on the topic of Site Reliability Engineering. In addition to SRE, Jason has authored books with O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media on the subject of post-incident reviews and Chatops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>