<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jason Hand</title>
    <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jason Hand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 08:53:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jasonhand.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Cate - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/scott_cate_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 08:53:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/scott_cate_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>The 2018&amp;frasl;2019 &amp;ldquo;Microsoft Ignite | The Tour&amp;rdquo; global event recently completed in Mumbai.
The event took place in 17 cities around the world. Myself and other advocates joined forces with MVPs and Microsoft product specialists and experts to share current thinking around how to build amazing systems and services in the cloud and how to keep them up and running reliably.
In the coming weeks I&amp;rsquo;ll provide a full retrospective on the event and the seven cities I had the pleasure of visiting while on tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/books/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christina Warren - Microsoft | Ignite Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/christina_warren__microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 08:58:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/christina_warren__microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Christina and I first met during the Cloud Advocate Summit right after I joined the team at Microsoft. We had a full day of speaker training and were paired up on our first excercise.
Personally knowing only a handful of people on the team prior to joining, I had researched a few people on the roster, Christina quickly surfaced in my online searches.
Host of &amp;ldquo;This week on Channel 9&amp;rdquo;, Christina is one of the most knowledgable and charismatic people I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Range SRE Meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/frontrangesre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/frontrangesre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rick Claus - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/rick_claus_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 10:03:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/rick_claus_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget my very first day on campus as a full-time Microsoft Azure Advocate.
Especially my first &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; meeting with members of my team - a discussion around the process of updating documentation found on Microsoft Docs!
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it. Here I was sitting around a table with others reviewing how we could submit changes and new content to online resources used by so many.
Leading the conversation was Rick Claus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Pulse</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/communitypulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:16:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/communitypulse/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Bugnion - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/laurent_bugnion_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:53:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/laurent_bugnion_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Laurent and I had the pleasure of taking part in the first two stops on last year&amp;rsquo;s Microsoft Ignite | The Tour in Berlin and Sau Paulo. Since then we&amp;rsquo;ve met up at a number of cities around the world.
A true polymath on technical topics, Laurent delivered a number of different sessions throughout the tour.
Be sure to check out some of the talks below as well as a few other areas Laurent likes to dabble in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevopsDays Rockies</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/gallery/devopsdaysrox/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Gordon - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/jay_gordon_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:54:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/jay_gordon_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Jay and I joined Microsoft around the same time and for a brief moment were even on the same team within the larger Cloud Advocacy team.
Every time we got to speak at the same stop on the Microsoft Ignite | The Tour, we tended to gravitate towards each other and despite vastly different tastes in music, we have a lot in common and it&amp;rsquo;s always good to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Likness - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/jeremy_likness_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:54:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/jeremy_likness_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen Jeremy give a talk, you start to understand just how much he knows about a large number of topics. Co-host of &amp;ldquo;On .NET&amp;rdquo;, Jeremy teaches me something new each time I interact with him.
Check out a couple of the presentations he gave during the Microsoft Ignite | The Tour in Amsterdam below.
Tour Presentations: Azure Fundamentals  DEV10 - Designing resilient cloud applications DEV50 - Investing in Serverless: less servers, more code  Hot Topics  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ari Bornstein - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/ari_bornstein_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:55:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/ari_bornstein_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Every time I get to hang out with Ari is a good work trip. The moment I saw him carrying around a copy of Daniel Kahneman&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Thinking Fast &amp;amp; Slow&amp;rdquo;, I knew we would get along well.
Aside from behavorial economic theory, Ari and I have had the pleasure of connecting on several stops during the Microsoft Ignite | The Tour and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to teaming up with him on a few artificial intelligence projects - something I&amp;rsquo;m starting to explore more myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damien Brady - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/damien_brady_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:56:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/damien_brady_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>When you chat with Damien about literally any topic, you quickly realize YOU KNOW NOTHING .. and ALSO, he&amp;rsquo;s really REALLY good at explaining things.
If you have a few minutes, give the &amp;ldquo;Using Artificial Intelligence to Augment Data&amp;rdquo; presentation from this past Microsoft Ignite | The Tour a watch. It was one of my favorites from the entire tour. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty crazy how easy it is to start using AI and Machine Learning to assist with different aspects of just about any business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Levick - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/ryan_levick_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:56:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/ryan_levick_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Ryan and I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a ton of opportunities to work together so far, but each time we do chat I realize I have a lot to learn. One specific area I want to learn more from Ryan about is on the topic of Rust.
He gave a great internal presentation on the benefits of using Rust, especially from an Operations-work point of view. The increased security aspect of it is enough to take a closer look if you are a traditional C# developer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erik St. Martin - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/erik_stmartin_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:57:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/erik_stmartin_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Hands-down&amp;hellip; the most amazing experience of this year&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Microsoft Ignite | The Tour&amp;rdquo; was riding along with Erik in a Ferrari 488 Spider through not only the streets of Milan but along Lake Como and up the mountain to the observatory.
Check out this video I made of the experience.
 You&amp;rsquo;d be hard pressed to find anyone who knows more about Kubernetes than Erik and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what he was in Amsterdam to talk about when we got another chance to hang out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Peterson - Microsoft Ignite | The Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/neil_peterson_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:57:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/neil_peterson_microsoft_ignite_tour_interview/</guid>
      <description>Neil and I had several really great trips together this year during the Microsoft Ignite | The Tour including a layover in Zermatt, Switzerland to snowboard the Matterhorn!
 A wizard at Kubernetes and continuous deployment techniques with Azure Devops, I learn something new from Neil each time I see one of his talks.
Check out a couple of the talks Neil delivered while in Amsterdam this past March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Long Strange Trip It&#39;s Been</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</guid>
      <description>Just over four years ago, I impulsively responded to a Facebook post about a devops evangelism role at a new tech startup.
I had never been an evangelist and I knew nothing of the term “devops”. #yolo ¯_(ツ)_/¯
This spontaneous act illuminated a path of personal and professional growth.
A path that created new opportunities for me almost daily.
A path that changed me for the better.
A path that wasn’t there… until it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Things</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/five-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 12:48:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/five-things/</guid>
      <description>5 – Things Developers Can Use To Go On-call (and Not Hate Their Life)  As service reliability and uptime become increasingly more important for organizations building applications, developers are now being exposed to new responsibilities and challenges.
Tiered ticketing processes, Network Operations Centers (NOC), along with traditional change and incident management technicques can’t provide the level of response necessary to support rapidly deployed applications requiring high availability and maximum uptime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Call Horror Stories</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/on-call-horror-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 15:28:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/on-call-horror-stories/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago while in New York City to speak at QCon, my buddy and co-worker (Jay Gordon) was nice enough to let me take over his home office to record a podcast with the ITSM Crowd.
While I was there, we decided it made perfect sense to record an episode of his show &amp;ldquo;On-call Horror Stories&amp;rdquo;, of which I have plenty to reminisce over.
However, we decided to take a different approach to the conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a Static Site from Azure App Service to Blob Storage</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/migrate_to_static_blob/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 13:58:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/migrate_to_static_blob/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITSM Crowd Podcast</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/itsm_crowd_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 13:19:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/itsm_crowd_podcast/</guid>
      <description>IT Service Management (ITSM) &amp;hellip; and devops share many of the same high level objectives, but often diverge on approach and language.
Some of that is starting to change, however.
Check out the conversation I had with Claire Agutter, and Doug Tedder on Site Reliability Engineering and how organizations are finding common ground when they start to talk about desired outcomes and value.
For more on the topic of SRE, check out the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Guru  and Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/cloud_guru_mitt_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 15:13:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/cloud_guru_mitt_2019/</guid>
      <description>  Microsoft Ignite | The Tour: Check out some additional interviews from
 Scott Cate Christina Warren Rick Claus Laurent Bugnion Jay Gordon Mel McKenna Jeremy Likness Ari Bornstein Juliet Friedman Damien Brady Ryan Levick Erik S. Martin Neil Peterson  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Road Trip - 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/devops_road_trip_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 14:19:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/devops_road_trip_2019/</guid>
      <description>In 2016, with the help of my amazing team at VictorOps, we put on the initial DevOps Road Trip - a series of events in several tech hubs around the U.S.
Starting off in Denver, we took our traveling event to Seattle, Minneapolis, San Francisco, and New York. Each of these free events were held at a unique and memorable venues.
In Denver, we invited attendees to Mile High Stadium (where the Denver Broncos play).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite | The Tour 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/mitt_fy19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 13:54:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/mitt_fy19/</guid>
      <description>Azure Fundamentals    Track Presentation     FUN10 - Discovering Microsoft Azure   FUN20 - Azure Networking Basics   FUN30 - Discovering Azure Tooling &amp;amp; Utilities   FUN40 - Azure Security Basics   FUN50 - Storing Data in Azure    Building and Maintaining Your Hybrid Cloud    Track Presentation     HYB10 - Planning and implementing hybrid network connectivity   HYB20 - Securing your Azure environment   HYB30 - Maintaining your environment   HYB40 - Governing your Azure environment   HYB50 - Business continuity planning    Building Your Applications for the Cloud    Track Presentation     DEV10 - Designing resilient cloud applications   DEV20 - Deploying your application faster and safer   DEV30 - Detecting application anomalies with Telemetry   DEV40 - Selecting the right data storage strategy for your cloud application   DEV50 - Investing in Serverless: less servers, more code    Getting the Most out of your Data    Track Presentation     DAT10 - Dealing with massive data ingestion   DAT20 - Operationalizing your new inventory management Machine Learning Model   DAT30 - Using artificial intelligence to augment data   DAT40 - Running Machine Learning experiments on inventory management   DAT50 - Operationalizing your new inventory management Machine Learning Model    Migrating Applications to the Cloud    Track Presentation     MIG10 - Migrating web applications to Azure   MIG20 - Moving your database to Azure   MIG30 - Deploying your application faster and safer   MIG40 - Modernizing your application with containers and Serverless   MIG50 - Consolidating infrastructure with Azure Kubernetes Service    Operating Applications &amp;amp; Infrastructure in the Cloud    Track Presentation     SRE10 - Modernizing your infrastructure: moving to Infrastructure as Code   SRE20 - Monitoring your infrastructure and applications in production   SRE30 - Diagnosing failure in the cloud   SRE40 - Scaling for growth and resiliency   SRE50 - Responding to and learning from failure    Check out some additional interviews from:  Scott Cate Christina Warren Rick Claus Laurent Bugnion Jay Gordon Mel McKenna Jeremy Likness Ari Bornstein Juliet Friedman Damien Brady Ryan Levick Erik S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Users through Site Reliability Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/empowering_users_through_site_reliability_engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 12:37:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/empowering_users_through_site_reliability_engineering/</guid>
      <description>When.. was the last time you got excited about new technology? What was it?
Was it a programming language?
Rust, Go, Node.js?
Maybe a new framework?
Angular, React?
Or was it something like serverless or containers?
Azure functions, Docker, Kubernetes?
Think back on what it was.
Do you have something in your mind?
Ok, now &amp;hellip;
How did you learn about it?
Likely from a friend or colleague introducing it to you, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minimum Viable Incident Response Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/minimum-viable-incident-response-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 12:31:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/minimum-viable-incident-response-plan/</guid>
      <description>Small Problem - Large Cost On Wednesday, August 1st 2012 an 18 year old financial services firm began a test run of their new trading software.
Carefully configured to interact with a very small number of stocks and with Buy and Sell points set well outside where the markets were trading that day, a reasonable amount of caution was taken to reduce the blast radius in the unlikely event anything should go wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Prometheus on Azure</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/installing_prometheus_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 08:27:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/blog/installing_prometheus_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>This post will walk through the basisc of getting Prometheus installed and configured on an Azure Virtual Machine (VM).
Create a new VM  Create a Virtual Machine  Basics Disks Networking Management   Add a custom domain  Custom DNS Create Virtual Network  Open Ports 22 and 9090   Connect to VM and install Prometheus  Remote Connection to VM Download &amp;amp; Install Promoetheus on VM Start Prometheus  Login to your Azure Portal Go to portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonhand.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jasonhand.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Jason Hand Senior Cloud Ops Advocate @ Microsoft Jason writes, presents, and coaches on the principles and nuance of DevOps, Site Reliability Engineering, and modern incident management practices. Named &amp;ldquo;DevOps Evangelist of the Year&amp;rdquo; by DevOps.com in 2016, Jason recently authored a new book on the topic of Site Reliability Engineering. In addition to SRE, Jason has authored books with O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media on the subject of post-incident reviews and Chatops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>