<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Jason Hand</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Jason Hand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Long Strange Trip It&#39;s Been</title>
      <link>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what_a_long_strange_trip_its_been/</guid>
      <description>Just over four years ago, I impulsively responded to a Facebook post about a devops evangelism role at a new tech startup.
I had never been an evangelist and I knew nothing of the term “devops”. #yolo ¯_(ツ)_/¯
This spontaneous act illuminated a path of personal and professional growth.
A path that created new opportunities for me almost daily.
A path that changed me for the better.
A path that wasn’t there… until it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Deployment Option</title>
      <link>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/configure_deployment_option/</guid>
      <description>Begin by selecting the &amp;ldquo;Choose Source&amp;rdquo; (Configure required settings) option Next select the correct source. I&amp;rsquo;m using GitHub, so that is the option I will choose:
The next screen will prompt you to enter your GitHub account, project, branch, etc.
Once you have made your configuration choices, select &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; at the bottom of the screen.
That&amp;rsquo;s it!
Now, any time new code is pushed to your repository, Azure will automatically deploy the changes for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy a Static HTML Site To Azure as a Web App</title>
      <link>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 15:26:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/deploy_static_html_site_to_azure_webapp/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial will walk you through getting a static web site up and running as a Web App on Microsoft Azure.
The site itself is stored in a GitHub repository:
https://github.com/jasonhand/JasonHandCom
The site is built using Hugo (gohugo.io)
The tutorial does not cover Hugo specific topics but rather automatically pushing changes to a site up to the cloud (MS Azure) automatically once code has been committed to the repository.
Open the Cloud Shell from within the Azure Portal</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>